<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daily Facts</string>
    <string name="fact_title_one">Hippopotamus Sweat is Red</string>
    <string name="fact_title_two">The Eiffel Tower Can Grow Taller in the Summer</string>
    <string name="fact_title_three">Octopuses Have Three Hearts</string>
    <string name="fact_title_four">A Day on Venus Is Longer Than a Year on Venus</string>
    <string name="fact_title_five">The Great Wall of China Is Over 13,000 Miles Long</string>
    <string name="fact_title_six">Bananas Are Berries, But Strawberries Aren\'t</string>
    <string name="fact_title_seven">Honey Never Spoils</string>
    <string name="fact_title_eight">The Shortest War in History Lasted 38 Minutes</string>
    <string name="fact_title_nine">The Sun\'s Mass Makes Up 99.86% of Our Solar System</string>
    <string name="fact_title_ten">A Group of Flamingos Is Called a Flamboyance</string>
    <string name="fact_title_eleven">Cows Have Best Friends</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twelve">The World\'s Largest Desert Used to Be a Sea</string>
    <string name="fact_title_thirteen">The Loudest Sound Ever Recorded Was a Volcanic Eruption</string>
    <string name="fact_title_fourteen">The Mantis Shrimp Can Punch with the Force of a Bullet</string>
    <string name="fact_title_fifteen">A Single Strand of Spaghetti Is Called a Spaghetto</string>
    <string name="fact_title_sixteen">A Cat\'s Brain Is 90% Similar to a Human\'s</string>
    <string name="fact_title_seventeen">Your Taste Buds Change Every 10 to 14 Days</string>
    <string name="fact_title_eighteen">Humans Share 50% of Their DNA with Bananas</string>
    <string name="fact_title_nineteen">Antarctica Is the World\'s Largest Desert</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty">The World\'s Oldest Known Recipe is for Beer</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_one">In the 16th Century, Turkish Women Could Initiate Divorce for Lack of Coffee</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_two">The First Recorded Game of Baseball Was in 1846</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_three">Lighters Were Invented Before Matches</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_four">The Coldest Temperature Ever Recorded on Earth Was -128.6°F</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_five">The Original Name of Bank of America Was "Bank of Italy"</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_six">Jellyfish Are 95% Water</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_seven">The Sun Emits Neutrinos Continuously</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_eight">The Most Common Language in the World Is Mandarin Chinese</string>
    <string name="fact_title_twenty_nine">Cleopatra Was Greek, Not Egyptian</string>
    <string name="fact_title_thirty">The Oldest Living Organism on Earth Is Over 80,000 Years Old</string>
    <string name="fact_description_one">Explore the intriguing fact that hippopotamus sweat is red.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_two">Learn why the Eiffel Tower can change height with the seasons.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_three">Dive into the biology of octopuses and their multiple hearts.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_four">Discover why a day on Venus is longer than a year on Venus.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_five">Uncover the incredible length of the Great Wall of China.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_six">Explore the surprising categorization of fruits.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_seven">Delve into the timeless properties of honey that never spoil.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_eight">Learn about the remarkably short Anglo-Zanzibar War.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_nine">Understand the massive contribution of the sun\'s mass in our solar system.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_ten">Find out what a group of flamingos is called.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_eleven">Discover the social connections of cows and their best friends.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twelve">Uncover the fascinating transformation of the world\'s largest desert.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_thirteen">Witness the power of volcanic eruptions and the loudest sound ever recorded.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_fourteen">Learn about the incredible punching power of the mantis shrimp.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_fifteen">Find out the singular form of spaghetti.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_sixteen">Discover the surprising similarity between a cat\'s brain and a human\'s.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_seventeen">Learn how your taste buds regularly change, affecting your palate.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_eighteen">Explore the genetic connection between humans and bananas.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_nineteen">Understand the frozen landscape of the world\'s largest desert, Antarctica.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty">Learn about the world\'s oldest known recipe for beer.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_one">Discover how coffee played a role in Turkish women\'s divorce rights in the 16th century.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_two">Find out about the first recorded game of baseball in 1846.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_three">Learn that lighters were invented before matches.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_four">Explore the chilling record of the coldest temperature on Earth.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_five">Discover the original name of Bank of America as "Bank of Italy."</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_six">Learn that jellyfish are composed of 95% water.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_seven">Explore the continuous emission of neutrinos by the sun.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_eight">Understand that the most common language in the world is Mandarin Chinese.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_twenty_nine">Learn that Cleopatra was of Greek descent, not Egyptian.</string>
    <string name="fact_description_thirty">Discover the incredible longevity of the world\'s oldest living organism.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_one">Hippopotamus sweat contains a red pigment, giving it a reddish hue.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_two">The Eiffel Tower can expand in height by up to 15 centimeters during the hotter summer months.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_three">Octopuses have three hearts: two pump blood to the gills, and one pumps it to the rest of the body.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_four">A day on Venus, due to its slow rotation, is actually longer than a year on Venus.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_five">The Great Wall of China stretches over 13,000 miles, making it the world\'s longest wall.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_six">Botanically, bananas are considered berries, while strawberries are not.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_seven">Honey has an indefinite shelf life and does not spoil, even after thousands of years.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_eight">The Anglo-Zanzibar War of 1896 holds the record for the shortest war, ending in just 38 minutes.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_nine">The mass of the sun makes up 99.86% of the total mass in our solar system.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_ten">A group of flamingos is referred to as a "flamboyance."</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_eleven">Cows form strong social bonds with other cows, often having best friends within their herds.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twelve">Antarctica, with its frozen landscape, is the world\'s largest desert, while the Sahara is the largest hot desert.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_thirteen">The loudest sound ever recorded was produced by the eruption of the Krakatoa volcano in 1883.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_fourteen">The mantis shrimp can deliver a punch with the force of a .22 caliber bullet, making it one of the fastest and most powerful predators in the ocean.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_fifteen">A single strand of spaghetti is known as a "spaghetto."</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_sixteen">A cat\'s brain is remarkably similar to a human\'s, sharing about 90% of its structure.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_seventeen">The taste buds on your tongue are replaced every 10 to 14 days, allowing your palate to evolve over time.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_eighteen">Humans share approximately 50% of their DNA with bananas, due to shared genetic building blocks.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_nineteen">Antarctica, with its frozen landscape, is the world\'s largest desert, while the Sahara is the largest hot desert.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty">The world\'s oldest known recipe, dating back over 3,900 years, is for beer and is recorded on a Sumerian tablet.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_one">In the 16th century, Turkish women could initiate divorce for lack of coffee from their husbands.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_two">The first recorded game of baseball took place in Hoboken, New Jersey, in 1846.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_three">Lighters were invented before matches. The first lighter was developed in the early 1820s, predating friction matches.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_four">The coldest temperature ever recorded on Earth was -128.6°F (-89.2°C) in Antarctica in 1983.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_five">The original name of Bank of America was "Bank of Italy" when it was founded in 1904.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_six">Jellyfish are composed of 95% water, which contributes to their gelatinous appearance.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_seven">The sun emits neutrinos continuously as a byproduct of its nuclear fusion processes.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_eight">Mandarin Chinese is the most commonly spoken language in the world, with over a billion native speakers.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_twenty_nine">Cleopatra, the famed queen of Egypt, was of Greek descent, not Egyptian.</string>
    <string name="fact_fact_thirty">The oldest living organism on Earth is a colony of quaking aspen trees in Utah, estimated to be over 80,000 years old.</string>
    <string name="day_format_string">Day %1$d</string>
</resources>